(insects chirping)
(upbeat music)
♪ I just wanna stay in
the sun where I find ♪
♪ I know it's hard sometimes ♪
♪ Pieces of peace in the
sun's peace of mind ♪
♪ I know it's hard sometimes ♪
♪ Yeah, I think about the
end just way too much ♪
♪ But it's fun to fantasize ♪
♪ On my enemies who
wouldn't wish who I was ♪
♪ But it's fun to fantasize ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Takin' my time on my ride ♪
♪ I'd die for you that's easy to say ♪
♪ We have a list of people
that we would take ♪
♪ A bullet for them, a bullet for you ♪
♪ A bullet for everybody in this room ♪
♪ But I don't seem to see
many bullets coming through ♪
♪ See many bullets coming through ♪
♪ Metaphorically, I'm the man ♪
♪ But literally, I
don't know what I'd do ♪
♪ I'd live for you and that's hard to do ♪
♪ Even harder to say, when
you know it's not true ♪
♪ Even harder to write,
when you know that's a lie ♪
♪ There were people back home
who tried talking to you ♪
♪ But then you ignore them still ♪
♪ All these questions
they're for real, like ♪
♪ Who would you live for ♪
♪ Who would you die for ♪
♪ And Would you ever kill ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Takin' my time on my ride ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much Help me ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much
I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much Help me ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much
I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm taking my time ♪
♪ Takin' my time on my ride ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
taking my time on my ride ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm fallin' so I'm
takin' my time on my ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much Help me ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much
I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much Help me ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much
I've been thinking too much ♪
♪ I've been thinking too much Help me ♪